export const GeneralQuiz = {
    title:['General Quiz'],
    questions: [
        {
            question: 'What language do you use with libraries such as React and Angular?',
            answer1: 'PHP',
            answer2: 'JAVA',
            answer3: 'JavaScript',
            answer4:'Python',
            correctAnswer: 'answer3',
            key: '1A',
        },
        {
            question: 'What markup language to you use to build a web page?',
            answer1: 'HTML',
            answer2: 'JAVA',
            answer3: 'Python',
            answer4:'C',
            correctAnswer: 'answer1',
            key: '2A',
        },
        {
            question: 'Wich one of these is a way to store multiple values in a single var?',
            answer1: 'string',
            answer2: 'array',
            answer3: 'number',
            answer4:'boolean',
            correctAnswer: 'answer2',
            key: '3A',
        },
        {
            question: 'How do you indicate values are not equal in JavaScript?',
            answer1: '===',
            answer2: '=>',
            answer3: '!==',
            answer4:'<=',
            correctAnswer: 'answer3',
            key: '4A',
        },
    ]
}

export const HtmlQuiz = {
    title:['HTML Quiz'],
    questions: [
        {
            question: 'What would be the best tag to use for a Title en HTML?',
            answer1: '<p>',
            answer2: '<h1>',
            answer3: '<a>',
            answer4:'<div>',
            correctAnswer: 'answer2',
            key: '1B',
        },
        {
            question: 'What tag is used to display a jpg file?',
            answer1: '<h1>',
            answer2: '<p>',
            answer3: '<img>',
            answer4:'C',
            correctAnswer: 'answer3',
            key: '2B',
        },
        {
            question: 'Wich one of these is a tag used to contain other HTML element?',
            answer1: '<div>',
            answer2: '<a>',
            answer3: '<img>',
            answer4:'h2',
            correctAnswer: 'answer1',
            key: '3B',
        },
        {
            question: 'Wich element is used for paragraph text?',
            answer1: '<h1>',
            answer2: '<a>',
            answer3: '<body>',
            answer4:'<p>',
            correctAnswer: 'answer4',
            key: '4B',
        },
        {
            question: 'Wich element is used for unorder list?',
            answer1: '<ol>',
            answer2: '<ul>',
            answer3: '<li>',
            answer4:'<dl>',
            correctAnswer: 'answer2',
            key: '5B',
        },
        {
            question: 'Wich HTML attribute  is used to define style information?',
            answer1: 'style',
            answer2: 'alt',
            answer3: 'src',
            answer4:'lang',
            correctAnswer: 'answer1',
            key: '6B',
        },
        {
            question: 'Wich HTML attribute is used to specify the path for an image?',
            answer1: 'style',
            answer2: 'alt',
            answer3: 'src',
            answer4:'lang',
            correctAnswer: 'answer3',
            key: '7B',
        },
    ]
}

export const JavaScriptQuiz = {
    title:['JavaScript Quiz'],
    questions:[
        {
            question: 'Wich of these allows you to declare a variable?',
            answer1: 'const',
            answer2: 'function',
            answer3: 'if',
            answer4:'for',
            correctAnswer: 'answer1',
            key: '1C',
        },
        {
            question: 'Wich of these is a special variable that can hold more than?',
            answer1: 'string',
            answer2: 'boolean',
            answer3: 'array',
            answer4:'conditional',
            correctAnswer: 'answer3',
            key: '2C',
        },
        {
            question: 'What do you use to execute a block of code a number of time?',
            answer1: 'a function',
            answer2: 'a loop',
            answer3: 'an object',
            answer4:'an array',
            correctAnswer: 'answer2',
            key: '3C',
        },
        {
            question: 'Wich data type can either be true or false?',
            answer1: 'a function',
            answer2: 'a variable',
            answer3: 'an array',
            answer4:'a boolean',
            correctAnswer: 'answer4',
            key: '4C',
        },
        {
            question: 'What do you use with Math.random() to return a random inte',
            answer1: 'an array',
            answer2: 'an object',
            answer3: 'Math.floor()',
            answer4:'Math.integer()',
            correctAnswer: 'answer3',
            key: '5C',
        },
    ]
}